(this["webpackJsonpteamsocial-quiz-azazelemjay"]=this["webpackJsonpteamsocial-quiz-azazelemjay"]||[]).push([[0],{24:function(e,t,r){},31:function(e,t,r){},32:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(1),n=r.n(s),a=r(16),i=r.n(a),o=(r(24),r(2));function c(e){var t={};return e.username.trim()?e.username.length<3?t.username="Username should be 3 characters or more":e.username.length>20&&(t.username="Username should be not be more 20 characters long"):t.username="Username required",t}var u=r(10),l=r(13),x=function(e,t){var r=Object(s.useState)({username:""}),n=Object(o.a)(r,2),a=n[0],i=n[1],c=Object(s.useState)({}),x=Object(o.a)(c,2),h=x[0],j=x[1],b=Object(s.useState)(!1),O=Object(o.a)(b,2),d=O[0],m=O[1];return Object(s.useEffect)((function(){0===Object.keys(h).length&&d&&e()}),[h]),{handleChange:function(e){var t=e.target,r=t.name,s=t.value;i(Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({},a),{},Object(u.a)({},r,s)))},handleSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault(),j(t(a)),m(!0)},values:a,errors:h}},h=r(0),j=function(e){var t=e.submitForm,r=x(t,c),s=r.handleChange,n=r.values,a=r.handleSubmit,i=r.errors;return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"Form",children:[Object(h.jsx)("header",{className:"App-header",children:Object(h.jsx)("h1",{children:"Majoro's Glorious Quiz"})}),Object(h.jsxs)("form",{className:"form",onSubmit:a,children:["Enter Player Name ",Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("label",{htmlFor:"username",children:"UserName: "}),Object(h.jsx)("input",{id:"username",type:"text",name:"username",placeholder:"enter user name",value:n.username,onChange:s}),i.username&&Object(h.jsx)("p",{children:i.username}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{type:"submit",onClick:function(){localStorage.setItem("name",n.username)},onSubmit:function(e){e.preventDefault()},children:"Start Game"})]})]})},b=r(3),O=r(19);function d(){var e=[{questionText:"Who is the main character of Bleach?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Byakuya Kuchiki",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Kenpachi Zaraki",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Ichigo Kurosaki",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Renji Abarai",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is the name of the king of the pirates in One Piece?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Bullet",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Sakazuki Akainu",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Monkey D. Luffy",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Gol D. Roger",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who is the armor titan in Attack On Titan?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Reiner",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Mikasa ",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Bertolt",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Levi",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is the masked man in Naruto Shippuden",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Minato Namikaze",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Madara Uchiha",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Obito Uchiha",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Sasuke Uchiha",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which element does Head Captain Yamamoto wield in Bleach?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Water",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Earth",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Air",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fire",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who killed Lelouche Lemperouge in Code Geass?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Suzaku Kururugi",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"CC",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Kaname Ohgi",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"None",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who did Naruto marry at the end of Naruto Shippuden?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sakura Haruno",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ino Yamanaka",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Hinata Hyuga",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Tenten",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of these anime series is not Shounen",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Bleach",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"One Punch Man",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Naruto",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Dragon Ball",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who is the main character in Fairy Tail?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Natsu Dragneel",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Lucy Heartfelia",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Erza Scarlett",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Grey Fullbuster",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Tensa Zangetsu is the name of Ichigo's Bankai",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(),r=Object(o.a)(t,2),n=(r[0],r[1]),a=Object(s.useState)(10),i=Object(o.a)(a,2),c=i[0],u=i[1],l=Object(s.useState)(e),x=Object(o.a)(l,2),j=x[0],b=x[1];function O(e){for(var t,r,s=e.length;s>0;)r=Math.floor(Math.random()*s),t=e[--s],e[s]=e[r],e[r]=t;return e}var d=Object(s.useState)(0),m=Object(o.a)(d,2),w=m[0],T=m[1],C=Object(s.useState)(!1),p=Object(o.a)(C,2),f=p[0],v=p[1],g=Object(s.useState)(0),S=Object(o.a)(g,2),q=S[0],y=S[1],k=JSON.stringify(localStorage.getItem("name")).replace('"',"").replace('"',""),N=" ";return N=q>=c/2?"You passed the quiz":"You failed the quiz",Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h1",{className:"header",children:"Anime Quiz"}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:f?Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:[" ",k," You scored ",q," out of ",c]}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),N]}):Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answers",children:[Object(h.jsx)("p",{children:"Select the number of questions for Your game"}),Object(h.jsxs)("select",{name:"option",onChange:function(t){if(n(t.target.value),u(t.target.value),5===c)O(e),e.splice(5,5),b(e);else if(7===c){O(e),e.splice(7,3),b(e)}else{O(e),e.splice(10,10),b(e)}return c},children:[Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"10",children:"All questions"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"5",children:"5"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"7",children:"7"})]})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:["Player Name: ",k]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-count",children:Object(h.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",w+1]})}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:j[w].questionText})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:[j[w].answerOptions.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){!0===e&&y(q+1);var t=w+1;t<c?T(t):v(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.answerText})})),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),"Your score is ",q]})]})})]})}function m(){var e=[{questionText:"Who is deemed the fastest man alive in sports?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Barry Allen",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chad le Claus",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Usain Bolt",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Pierro Maximoff",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which soccer player has scored the most goals ever?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Ronaldhino",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Christiano Ronaldo",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Neymar",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Messi",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"After how many Year\u2019s FIFA World Cup is held??",answerOptions:[{answerText:"4 years",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"2 years",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"3 years",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Every year",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"a typical golf course has how many holes?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"9",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"12",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"18",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"7",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"after how many years are the olympic games held?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"5",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"2",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"3",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"4",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who had started the International Women\u2019s Boxing Hall of Fame?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Terri Moss",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Sue TL Fox",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Claressa Shields",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Barbara Buttrick",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which among the following is known as 'Bible of Cricket'?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"All Out Cricket",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cricinfo Magazine",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Wisden",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"The Guide to Cricketers",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which country has won the maximum number of medals in the all time history of Commonwealth Games?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Australia",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"England",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"India",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Canada",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"There are 30 balls in the game of snooker.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"There has never been a woman chess master.",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(),r=Object(o.a)(t,2),n=(r[0],r[1]),a=Object(s.useState)(10),i=Object(o.a)(a,2),c=i[0],u=i[1],l=Object(s.useState)(e),x=Object(o.a)(l,2),j=x[0],b=x[1];function O(e){for(var t,r,s=e.length;s>0;)r=Math.floor(Math.random()*s),t=e[--s],e[s]=e[r],e[r]=t;return e}var d=Object(s.useState)(0),m=Object(o.a)(d,2),w=m[0],T=m[1],C=Object(s.useState)(!1),p=Object(o.a)(C,2),f=p[0],v=p[1],g=Object(s.useState)(0),S=Object(o.a)(g,2),q=S[0],y=S[1],k=JSON.stringify(localStorage.getItem("name")).replace('"',"").replace('"',""),N=" ";return N=q>=c/2?"You passed the quiz":"You failed the quiz",Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h1",{className:"header",children:"Sports Quiz"}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:f?Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:[" ",k," You scored ",q," out of ",c]}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),N]}):Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answers",children:[Object(h.jsx)("p",{children:"Select the number of questions for Your game"}),Object(h.jsxs)("select",{name:"option",onChange:function(t){if(n(t.target.value),u(t.target.value),5===c)O(e),e.splice(5,5),b(e);else if(7===c){O(e),e.splice(7,3),b(e)}else{O(e),e.splice(10,10),b(e)}return c},children:[Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"10",children:"All questions"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"5",children:"5"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"7",children:"7"})]})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:["Player Name: ",k]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-count",children:Object(h.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",w+1]})}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:j[w].questionText})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:[j[w].answerOptions.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){!0===e&&y(q+1);var t=w+1;t<c?T(t):v(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.answerText})})),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),"Your score is ",q]})]})})]})}function w(){var e=[{questionText:"Who says this line in Avengers EndGame, 'You could not live with your own failure, could you..'",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Stephen Strange",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"He Who Remains",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Thanos",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Nick Fury",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Who was the true villain in Zack Snyder's Justice League?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Steppenwolf",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"The Mother Box",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Superman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Darkseid",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"what is the highest grossing movie of all time?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Avatar",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Avengers Endgame ",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Titanic",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Star Wars: Episode VII - The Force Awakens",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which Marvel series is currently streaming this month?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"HawkEye",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Loki",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"What If..?",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Wandavision",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Which of these Marvels movies is not set to be released in 2021?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Eternals",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Spider-man: No Way Home",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Black Widow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Dr. Strange: Multitude Of Madness",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who plays Peter Quill in Guardians Of The Galaxy?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Dave Bautista",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chris Evans",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chris Hemsworth",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chris Pratt",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Who is the actor behind Groot from the guardians of the galaxy?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sylvester Stallone",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Dwayne Johnson",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Morgan Freeman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Vin Diesel",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Red Skull Guards the soul stone in Avengers Infinity War",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Tony Stark said the line, 'You're not the only one cursed with knowledge'",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Tom Holland's first appearance in Marvel as spiderman was in Captain America Civil War ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"False",isCorrect:!1}]}],t=Object(s.useState)(),r=Object(o.a)(t,2),n=(r[0],r[1]),a=Object(s.useState)(10),i=Object(o.a)(a,2),c=i[0],u=i[1],l=Object(s.useState)(e),x=Object(o.a)(l,2),j=x[0],b=x[1];function O(e){for(var t,r,s=e.length;s>0;)r=Math.floor(Math.random()*s),t=e[--s],e[s]=e[r],e[r]=t;return e}var d=Object(s.useState)(0),m=Object(o.a)(d,2),w=m[0],T=m[1],C=Object(s.useState)(!1),p=Object(o.a)(C,2),f=p[0],v=p[1],g=Object(s.useState)(0),S=Object(o.a)(g,2),q=S[0],y=S[1],k=JSON.stringify(localStorage.getItem("name")).replace('"',"").replace('"',""),N=" ";return N=q>=c/2?"You passed the quiz":"You failed the quiz",Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h1",{className:"header",children:"Movies Quiz"}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:f?Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:[k," You scored ",q," out of ",c," ",Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),N]}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{children:"Restart Game"}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{children:"Choose a different Category"})]}):Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answers",children:[Object(h.jsx)("p",{children:"Select the number of questions for Your game"}),Object(h.jsxs)("select",{name:"option",onChange:function(t){if(n(t.target.value),u(t.target.value),5===c)O(e),e.splice(5,5),b(e);else if(7===c){O(e),e.splice(7,3),b(e)}else{O(e),e.splice(10,10),b(e)}return c},children:[Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"10",children:"All questions"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"5",children:"5"}),Object(h.jsx)("option",{value:"7",children:"7"})]})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("p",{children:["Player Name: ",k]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-count",children:Object(h.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",w+1]})}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:j[w].questionText})]}),Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:[j[w].answerOptions.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){!0===e&&y(q+1);var t=w+1;t<c?T(t):v(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.answerText})})),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),"Your score is ",q]})]})})]})}var T=function(){return Object(h.jsx)("div",{children:Object(h.jsx)(O.a,{children:Object(h.jsxs)(b.c,{children:[Object(h.jsx)(b.a,{path:"/Sports",exact:!0,component:m}),Object(h.jsx)(b.a,{path:"/Anime",exact:!0,component:d}),Object(h.jsx)(b.a,{path:"/Movies",exact:!0,component:w}),Object(h.jsx)(b.a,{path:"/LoginForm",exact:!0,component:j}),Object(h.jsx)(b.a,{path:"/",component:function(){var e=JSON.stringify(localStorage.getItem("name")).replace('"',"").replace('"',""),t=Object(b.f)();return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(h.jsxs)("h1",{children:["Make Your Pick Category ",e]}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return t.push("./Anime")},children:"Anime"}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return t.push("./Movies")},children:"Movies"}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return t.push("./Sports")},children:"Sports"}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("br",{}),Object(h.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return t.push("./LoginForm")},children:"Logout"})]})}})]})})})},C=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)(!1),t=Object(o.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1];return Object(h.jsx)(h.Fragment,{children:r?Object(h.jsx)(T,{}):Object(h.jsx)(j,{submitForm:function(){n(!0)}})})};r(31);var p=function(){return Object(h.jsx)(C,{})},f=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,33)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,a=t.getLCP,i=t.getTTFB;r(e),s(e),n(e),a(e),i(e)}))};i.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(p,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),f()}},[[32,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.714bc492.chunk.js.map